Uh so the general rule of thumb is is be ready for Europe, so you're ready for the rest of the world.
In Europe, no, right?
Right.
Yeah.
Uh I'll give it I'll give it a try, but it's it's uh not an easy an easy answer.
But indeed, um, you know, it's always known that Europe uh uh the Europe regulates and the US innovates.
And so uh it's it's much easier to uh to to start launch and be a little bit more risk taking in the US.
However, as soon as you touch a European citizen, you face the European law as well.
And so by default, you need to be ready for it.
And I think it is good because uh even though it's strict, they have I think very respectful uh laws for the consumers, which I would want to be applied to my data for sure as well.
Uh so the general rule of thumb is is be ready for Europe, so you're ready for the rest of the world.